(Penny:)Yeah.
(Bert:)-Well, see ya.
-You forgot your quartz.
(Bert:)Oh, it's okay.
I want you to have it.
(Leonard:)Bye.
(Amy:)He's nice.
(Howard:)Yeah, he's nice
because he likes you.
(Amy:)What?
(Amy:)-No, he doesn't.
-He brought you a pretty rock.
(Amy:)So? He does that every day--
Oh.
(Howard:)You know, if you'd
rather skip lunch
(Howard:)and hang out with your boyfriend,
Bert, it's totally okay.
(Amy:)He's not my boyfriend.
(Raj:)Are you sure?
He's tall, pale and awkward.
(Raj:)That sounds like your type.
(Amy:)Should someone as lonely as you
really be making fun of me?
(Raj:)Yeah, grow up, Howard. God.
(Amy:)What do I do?
I don't want to hurt his feelings.
(Howard:)Maybe the problem is
he thinks you're available.
(Howard:)Does he know
you're dating Sheldon?
(Amy:)I guess it hasn't come up.
(Howard:)There you go.
(Raj:)And does Sheldon know
you're dating Sheldon?
(Amy:)I'm sorry. Who are you dating?